Now I know what you're thinking. 20 million kuva. Wow, this guy must be mentally sound and an all-around well-adjusted human being.
Are you seriously farming kuva again?
NO, I'M WATCHING
*GOOD LORD*
GET OUT.
Contrary to popular belief, 40 Benadryls will do more than just let you see God.
If you don't know what this video is about, then let me catch you up to speed.  You see, a couple years ago,
I made a mistake.
*Schizophrenic rambling*
A year later, I made the same mistake.
Oh, I smell kuva in the air
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
And now,
I'm gonna do it again.
In today's chaotic evil carcinogenic experience,
I'll do more than just engage with self-destructive behavior.
I'm going to rapidly
abandon any principles and habits
that lead to a better life.